all right, sweetheart.
we are near najaf.
우리는 지금 나자프 근처야 (나자프 외곽, 이라크)
i'm not allowed to say exactly where.
정확히 어디인지는 못 말하고
hey, dwight, say hello to jenny.
드와잇, 제니한테 인사해
- he's cheating on you!
- nice.
- 너한테 바람피우고 있어
-그래
with a camel-- a drunk, slutty camel.
낙타랑, 술 취하고, 걸래 같은 낙타랑
all right, look, it was one time, okay,
한번 뿐이었어
난한테 계속 문자 보내고 있지만 끝이야
and the camel's been texting me,
but it's over, i promise.
hello? psd.
야~
PSD야 (민간 부문 개발)
hey come on??
you see those guys?
저기 사람들 보이지?
개인 청부업자들이야
private contractors.
they make 700 bucks a day.
하루에 700 달러를 벌지
i make 7.
난 7 달러 벌어
hey, yeah, but you know
what they got to do?
야, 근데 저 사람들은 뭐 해야 하는지 알아?
they got to --
재내들은...
dwight!
...they got to do?
they got to--
dwight!
jenny your fiancee?
제니가 약혼자 인가요?
well, she was, but...
이었어요...하지만...
oh. oh, i'm sorry.
- 죄송해요
-괜찮아요, 뭐 그렇죠
i'm not mad. it happens.
look, i don't want charity.
-자선 같은 건원하지 않아요
-우린 자선사업 같은 거 아니에요
we are not a charity.
(leverage s01e02)
i just want my rehab.
전 그냥 재활만 원해요
and if i'm gonna work --
and i want to work --
만약 제가 일을 할 거면
그리고 일 하고 싶어요
dr. laroque says i need another
year and a half of hard-core rehab,
의사 선생님께서 최소한 일 년의 힘든 재활이 필요하데요
그리고 최소한 2번의 수술도요
maybe two more surgeries.
castleman shot me up.
케슬멘이 절 이렇게 만들어 놨어요
그냥 병원비만 처리 했으면 해요
i just want them to pay my bills.
no more, no less.
더 이상도, 더 이하도 아니에요
hmm.
the army investigation
determined you were --
군데 조사에 의하면
근데 그들은 반란군한테 맞았다 하던데요?
what, they said you were hit by insurgents?
yeah, that's because castleman refused
to cooperate in that investigation.
네, 그건 케슬멘이 조사에 비협력적으로 나와서 그래요
and they can do that?
-그럼 그렇게 할 수 있어요?
아무도 뭐라 하지 않던데요
no one's stopping them.
they're cowboys. they go off
all the time -- boom, boom.
그들은 무법자들이에요
자기 하고 싶은 데로 하죠
you know,
i just want them to do right by me.
전 그냥 저 때문에 올바른 일을 했으면 해요
pardon me, mr., uh...
-실례 합니다...미스터...
-네이슨 포드에요
oh, uh, nathan ford.
you're dr. lar--
-로로크 의사 선생님 이셨죠?
-밖에서 이야기좀 할까요?
could i talk to you outside?
doc, he's cool.
i found him on the internet.
선생님 괜찮아요
인터넷에서 찾았어요
yes, that never goes badly.
인터넷이 항상 좋은 게 아니잖아요
밖으로 오세요
with me.
uh, yeah.
i'll be in touch.
연락할께요
www.1000fr.com presents
capture:frm@룸琯
sync:frs@倒雷
you can't just come in here
and get his hopes up.
이렇게 그냥 와서 기대를 갖게 하자 마세요
you know, i'm just here to provide options.
-전 그냥 선택권을 주려고 왔어요
-선택권은 없어요
- there are no options!
- the veterans hospital --
-퇴역 군인 병원이
-6킬로미터 떨어져 있고 500 대기자가 있어요
...is 400 miles away and
has a 5-month waiting list.
everybody in that rehab room is a reservist.
재활 방에 있는 모두는 예비군이에요
when reservists get out,
they get sent home,
예비군이 퇴원하면 집으로 보내지지요
no matter where home is
그들의 집이 어디든지
치료가 필요한 곳에서 얼마나 멀든지 상관 없이요
or how far it is from
the treatment they need.
nobody thought this through.
많이 준비 된 게 없어요
우린 부유한 병원이 아니거든요
we're not a rich hospital.
i cashed in every favor i had
전 이들이 최대한 오랫동안 돌볼 수 있게 최대한 노력을 했어요
to take care of these kids
for as long as i could but --
i have to go back in there
전 페리한테 가서 더 이상 치료 할 수가 없다고 말해줘야 해요
and tell perry we can't treat him anymore.
i have to do that.
그 말을 제가 해야돼요
run your scam on somebody with money.
-돈 있는 사람한테 사기 치세요
-사기가 아니에요
it's not a scam. i'm here to help.
도와주려고 왔어요
people don't just show up to help.
그냥 도와주려는 사람은 없어요
세상은 그렇지 않죠
that's not the way the world works.
hardison, call them.
하디슨, 전화해
why?
왜요?
i can't live like this anymore!
전 더 이상 이렇게 살 수가 없어요
the lies and the filth!
거짓말과 이 불겸함!
no! help me! i just --
안 돼! 절 도와주세요!
전 순결해지고 싶어요
i want to be clean.
i want to be clean!
전 순결해지고 싶어요
할리우드
hollywood
yeah.
이게 비누 광고라는 건 아시는 거죠?
you understand this is
a soap commercial, right?
uh-huh.
네
well, when i thought about peggy,
페기에 대해서 생각해봤을 때요
i came up with this idea
that the dirt is really this giant,
때가 죄의 큰 은유라는 생각을 했어요
like, metaphor for sin.
you should take that.
전화 받으세요
no, no. you should take that.
받아 보세요
hello?
여보세요
when?
언제?
peggy killed her first husband.
페기가 첫 남편을 죽였어요
th-thank you.
베를린
berlin
is that you or me????
내꺼니 네꺼니?
it could be important.
중요한 거 같은데
does your mama have your number?
엄마 전화 아닐까?
yeah.
네?
nothing. why?
없어요. 왜요?
모나코
monago
parker.
파커입니다
oh, sh-- no, i wasn't shushing you.
당신한테 그런 거 아니에요
los angeles
로스앤젤레스
- from the first job?
- yeah.
-처음 했던 일 때?
-응
i put all that money
in a swiss bank account.
스위스 은행에 돈 다 넣었어
millions of dollars,
you didn't buy anything?
-백만 달러인데 아무것도 안 샀어?
-물건 같은 거 싫어. 돈이 좋아
i don't like stuff. i like money.
i bought a little retirement home in ireland...
난 자그마한 섬에 퇴직하면 살 집을 샀어
???
and dubai and tokyo.
두바이에도
그리고 도쿄에도
- what about you?
- yeah...
너는
i'm not about to
tell two known thieves
잘 알려진 두 명의 도둑한테 백만 달러 돈 번거로 뭐 했는지 알려줄 꺼 같아?
what i did with my
multimillion-dollar payout.
don't you trust us?
우릴 못 믿는 건가?
레버러지 컨설턴트
okay.
i don't get it.
-이해가 안가 /br -이게 뭐야?
what is this?
this is our new cover story.
이게 우리의 새로운 이름이에요
welcome to leverage
consulting & associates,
1913 위대한 하렌 레버러지 3세가 새운
레버러지 컨설턴트에 오신 걸 환영합니다
founded in 1913 by the great
harlan leverage iii.
i'm sorry.
미안
넌 네이슨한테 죽었다
nate is going to kill you.
did you paint that?
-네가 그렸니?
-난 천재야
i'm gifted.
that's weird.
이상해
now, leverage consulting is squeaky clean.
레버러지 컨설턴트는 깨끗해
기록에 있는 과거 90년의 기업 세금은 모두 납세 했어요
all corporate taxes are on record
as paid for the last 90 years.
all your identities as partners.
모든 신분은 회사 파트너로 되어있고
급여 세금은 모두 납세 되었어요
payroll taxes are paid.
you guys have pension plans and dental.
또한 연금하고 보험도 있고요
those are employment records,
파일들은 고용 기록하고, 케이스 내용하고, 회사 회보에요
case files, and company newsletters.
in 1998, i won the sack race
at the fourth of july picnic.
1998년 광복절 소풍 때 내가 마대 경주에서 일등 했대!
- cool!
- now, these --
그리고 여긴
these are your offices.
사무실이에요
now, you can bring something,
like a photo or,
사진 같은 거 가지고 와도 되요
you know what, a plant.
i'm a big supporter of dandelions.
아니면 꽃 같은 거도 되요
전 민들레가 좋아요!
hardison.
하디슨, 이거 꾸미는데 네 돈은 사용했다는 게 믿을 수 없어
i can't believe you spent your
share of the cash on all of this.
me, no. hell no.
nate paid for all of this,
나? 당연히 아니죠
네이슨이 돈 다 냈어요
you know, with what he had left.
남아 있는 걸로요
i mean, you know, after
he gave the rest of it away.
기부 하고 남은 돈으로요
whoa. what do you mean?
-기부 했다니, 무슨 말이요
-응, 모두
- he gave it away?
- yeah.
all of it, every last penny.
1원 모두
it was, uh, to, like,
어떤 어린이 병원인가
like some childrens hospital
or something like that, but...
이게 나의 걸작이지
this...
this is my masterpiece.
nice.
좋은데
my man.
long version or the short version?
-길해 설명할까요, 짧게 설명할까요?
-짧게
short.
-최대한 짧은 걸로
- short version.
- shortest.
photo and video forensics programs,
사진, 영상 수사 프로그램, 세계의 모든 은행 전산 연결
back doors into every electronic
banking system in the world,
running heuristic data crawlers all
over the news sites to find our clients.
그리고 우리 의뢰인을 찾을 뉴스 웹사이트 검색 기능과
oh, also...
-또한
-이게 짧은 거야?
this is the short version?
...facial recognition database
tied into cia, nsa, and the fbi.
CIA, NSA와 FBI에 연결된 얼굴 인식 시스템도
but the real pi?e de r?istance...
하지만 최고봉은
...directv hd total sports package --
HDTV 스카이 라이프 스포츠 채널이지
미식축구, 농구 그리고.. 하키 조금 좋아하니 그것도 넣었어요
nfl, nba...
and i threw in a little bit of hockey
'cause i know you people like that.
hockey.
하키라니
all right, stop kicking the tires.
그만 말만 하지 말고
you want to take her for a spin?
한번 시험 해볼까?
you see those guys?
저기 사람들 보이지?
개인 청부업자들이야
private contractors.
they make 700 bucks a day.
하루에 700 달러를 벌지
i make 7.
난 7 달러 벌어
hey, yeah, but you know
what they got to do?
야, 근데 저 사람들은 뭐 해야 하는지 알아?
they got to --
재내들은...
dwight!
our client is the cameraman,
의뢰인은 카메라 찍고 있는 사람이야
corporal robert perry.
로버트 페리 상등병
he says that the castleman
contractors spooked
그의 말에 의하면 케슬멘 청부업자들이 놀라서
and started firing.
총 쏘기 시작 했대
5.56 nato rounds...
나토 5.56 구 에요
9미리 반자동 기관총 총알과 섞였네요
mixed in with some 9 mills
from the submachine guns.
insurgents would have used
ak-47 with 7.62 ammo --
반란군은 7.62 총알의 AK-47 총을 사용하죠
has more of a "crack."
“크랙” 하는 소리를 좀 더 가지고 있어요
contractors shot them up, all right.
-청부업자들이 총을 쏜 것이 확실해요
-총 소리만 듣고 총을 알 수 있어?
you i.d.'d the weapon
from the gunshot sound.
it has a very distinctive sound.
뚜렷한 소리를 가지고 있어
castleman security is hard-core, folks,
케슬멘 경비는 최강이에요
a billion-dollar company.
억 단위 회사고 미군이 배치된 곳 모두 정부랑 계약했어요
they got fat government contracts
everywhere we got troops.
that's charles dufort, c.e.o.
회장인 챨스 듀포트에요
he's very paranoid
and very professional.
아주 편집적이고 프로페션널하지
i want to get this clear right now.
이건 집고 넘어가요
상대할 회사는 개인 군대 수준이에요
this is a private army
you're talking about taking on.
they got their own intel assets.
회사 정보 시스템이 있고 빽도 많아요
they got a lot of trigger-pullers.
yes, and lobbyists in
every office in washington, d.c.
맞아. 그리고 워싱턴의 모든 사무실에 로비스트도 있어
the problem with a cover-up
우릴 숨기는데 가장 큰 문제는
진짜같이 보이게 하는 서류들이야
is all the paperwork it takes
to keep the lies straight.
internal e-mails, memos.
내부 메일과 메모..
정확해
exactly.
- so...
- let's go to work.
-그럼
-시작하지
so, we steal the evidence
and threaten to expose them.
-그럼 증거를 훔쳐서 모든 걸 폭로 한다고 협박 하는 건가요?
- blackmail.
- ah, yes...
-공갈협박
-맞아
but just enough blackmail
to pay for perry's rehab --
페리와 백만 명의 손해를 보상할 수 있는 정도의 공갈협박 정도
maybe a couple of million more in damages.
never hold up in court.
-법정에서는 허용이 안될꺼에요
-그렇기 때문에 페리 상등병이 운이 좋은 거야
ah, but that's why
corporal perry is lucky.
he doesn't have lawyers.
he has thieves.
변호사를 고용한 게 하니라, 도둑을 고용한 거지
hardison.
하디슨!
케슨멜 경비는 로버트 젠킨스 하원의원을 환영합니다
사적인 파티입니다. 입장권 필요함
next time, i wear the suit.
다음엔 정장 입을꺼에요
dufort's here.
i'll make contact.
저에요. 접촉했어요
see what you can squeeze out of him.
뭘 짜낼 수 있는지 확인해봐
parker, hardison, time to hit his office.
파커, 하디슨, 사무실 들어가 볼까?
오피스 되돌아 가봐야되. 뭐 방금 생각났어
(케슬멘 본부)
i-i got to go back to the office.
i-i just remembered something.
what?
뭔데?
i just remembered gravity...
방금 중력하고 네 몸 덩어리가 생각나서
and the squishiness
of all my manly bits.
i designed this rig myself.
이거 내가 다 준비했어
the line is carbon fiber,
five-point harness.
줄은 탄소 섬유고, 요기 요기 등등 5개의 무개를 지탱할 멜빵이 있고
weight support here, here, and here,
autobraking resistance
on the main pulley back here.
이 뒤에 자동 멈춤 장치도 있어
okay. okay. c-cool.
so it's tested?
응, 알겠어
-그럼 시험 해본거지?
-아직
not yet.
not y--
아직? 언제 해볼 건데?
well, when the hell
was you gonna test it?
ohh!
you big baby.
아기 같으니라고
seriously?
아 진짜로
okay, hardison, parker, guard
sweeps are every 10 minutes.
파커, 하디슨 경비원들이 매 10분마다 경계를 돌아
정확히 9분 30분 남았어
that means you got 9 minutes, 30 seconds.
i'm working on it.
하고 있어요
castleman is gonna be very happy
with the new appropriations bill.
케슬멘은 새로운 세출 예산안 보고 아주 좋겠습니다
- pardon me, congressman.
- yes.
실례합니다, 하원의원님
lily mcready. i'm with executive orders.
익제기티브 오더스의 릴리 멕크레디입니다.
they're a london-based
defense contractor.
런던에 있는 방위 산업체라고 합니다
찰스 듀포트라 합니다
- charles dufort.
- oh.
executive orders doesn't
work for the u.s. government.
-익제기트브 오더스는 미 정부랑 같이 일 안하는 걸로 알고 있습니다만
-아직이요
yet.
perhaps we could do something about that.
그거에 대해서 어떻게 해볼까요?
yes, well, um, it was
very nice to meet you.
만나서 반가웠습니다
now, you'll have to excuse me.
전 실례하겠습니다
you're not poaching, are you?
가로채려는 건 아니겠죠?
appropriations bill 718.
세출 예산안 718. 저희 국방 계약입니다
그냥 물러나시죠
those are our defense contracts.
don't even bother.
mr. dufort, surely there's
enough war to go around.
듀포트시, 전쟁은 충분하다고요
i rather like you.
마음에 드는데요
hardison, hardison, what's ...
하디슨, 그들이 말하는 안이 무슨 안이야?
what's this bill they are talking abuot?
you know, i'd like to
give you the schoolhouse rock,
저도 한번 보고 싶은데 지금 전 보안 뚫는데 모든 전력을 쓰고 있어 바빠요
but this man has an rfid security-card
reader on his power supply,
so i'm a little busy.
ooh, old-school.
오~ 구식이네. 금고 찾았어
i found a safe.
you're not gonna believe this.
믿을 수가 없네. 음성 인식이야
it's voice-activated.
all right, well,
one problem at a time.
하나씩 해결하자. 소피, 나 간다
ur, sophie, i'm going in.
we need to get an rfid card to eliot.
당신은 전자태그 카드를 엘리엇한데 줘
my company's focused on meeting senators,
제 회사는 상원의원들을 만나는데 집중하지만
전 하원들 생각중이에요
but i'm thinking congressmen.
you know the great thing about congressmen?
하원의원 들이 좋은 점이 뭔지 아세요?
50, 100 grand well spent
will get one elected.
5만이나 10만 달러 잘 사용하면 당선 가능하죠
but then, once they're in,
하지만 당선되면 재선 율이 90프로 넘어요
the incumbency rate is over 95%.
so you can get, on an average,
그래서 한명 당선되면 18에서 20년 정도 사용 할 수 있죠
18, 20 years of use out of one of them.
in these uncertain times,
이런 힘든 기간에는
buying a united states congressman
미 하원의원을 구하는 게 한 회사가 할 수 있는 최상의 투자죠
is one of the best investments
a corporation can make.
ohh, i just threw up
in my mouth a little bit.
방금 조금 신물 나왔다
i'm a professional criminal,
and i find that disturbing.
전 전문 도둑인데, 방금 말한 건 너무한데
???
저희는 군 자문과 국제 보조는 40년 넘게 해왔어요
well,???
자기 정부를 전복하는데 도와주는 거죠, 듀포씨
no, overthrowing the government
is too harsh a way to describe it.
정부를 전복하는 건 너무 거칠게 표현하는 거고요
we just help them along.
그냥 도와 주는 거죠
it was a ??
협동이라 볼 수 있죠
??
-그런 거라 생각하세요? -저기
???
소스가 묻었어요
- ??
- ???
???
좋은 재킷에 소스가 많이 묻었네요
shouldn't be too hard to get out and wash.
닦는데 그리 힘들지 않을 거예요
oh??
oh, this is the first day i've worn it.
오늘 처음 입었는데. 감사해요
thank you.
let me see if i can get someone
to help you with that. excuse me.
도와 줄 수 있는 사람 있나 볼께요
- yeah, garcon?
- yes, ma'am?
could you, uh,
could you possibly help us?
도와 줄 수 있어요? 재킷에 얼룩이 묻었어요
- we've got a little stain on this jacket.
- ??oh look at that.
아 그러네요. 제가 해결할께요
- let me take care of that for you.
- ??
- if you ??
- let me, uh, keep this.
이건 가지고 갈게요. 저의 위치에 있는 사람이 지갑을 깜빡 하면 안 되죠
a man in my position
shouldn't forget his wallet.
that's embarrassing.
thank you.
here you go, sir.
knock yourself out.
요기요, 다 드세요
there's no magnetic strip.
자석 줄무늬가 없어
it's a little radio frequency.
무선 주파수를 내보내
just... just put it up next to
the phone that i gave you.
내가준 전화 옆에 놓아봐
복제 완료
보내는 중
i'm in.
들어왔다
parker, what's the status
of the voice lock?
파커, 음성인식 금고는 어떻게 되어가?
i've been sampling dufort's speech,
듀포트 음성을 표본화 하고 있지만 음성 몇 개가 더 필요해요
but i still need a few more sounds.
how many?
몇 개?
oh, i only need the sounds
"puh," "tuh," "ooh," "uh,"
퍼, 터, 우, 오, 에, 오, 아, 크, 에, 에프 음성만 필요해요
"eh," "oh," "ah,"
"kuh," "ay," "eff."
ah, only those.
그게 다야?
eliot?
-엘리엇?
-가요
i'm on it.
hello.
- ooh.
- mmm.
appetizer, sir?
애피타이저 드실래요?
sure. what have you got?
뭐 있어요?
i've got the p?es d'escargot
avec beurre d'argentine...
퍼테 에스타고 아베 알젠틴하고 오래된 오리같이 보이는거요
and what looks like
old duck, kind of greasy.
조금 기름이 많네요
i guess i'll have the first one.
첫 번째 꺼 먹을게요
but of course.
well?
먹어봐도 될까요?
may i have some?
the greasy duck?
기름 많은 오리요?
ooh, no, no, no, no, no.
-아니요, 기름 많은 오리는 먹지마세요
-추천하지 않아요
i wouldn't have the greasy duck.
no, i wouldn't suggest it.
no, the other one!
아니요! 딴거요
the p?es d'escargot
with the beurre argentine!
퍼테 에스타고 아베 알젠틴요!
excellent choice.
좋은 선택 이십니다
pretty good. you got most of them.
좋은데, 대부분 얻었어
okay, now all i need is
"eff," "uh," and "kuh."
이제 필요한건 에프, 어 하고 커야
this is shrimp!
새우 잔아
???
it's shrimp, you stupid fu--
새우 잔아 병신아!
ohh! there they are.
됐네
really loud, too.
근데 소리가 너무 커
okay, sophie, start the walkaway.
소피 나갈 준비해
i was wondering,
could i drop by your office?
-혹시 사무실에 잠시 들려도 될까요?
-아무 때나 오세요
anytime.
where are you going?
어디가?
playing a hunch.
직감이 있어서요
all right, well, play it fast.
그래? 그럼 빨리해
hardison, what do you got?
you got three minutes.
하디슨 3분 남았어
too much.
그정도면 충분해요
페리의 모든 치료 기록 얻었어요
i got all of perry's medical records.
??sure, that's --
that's pretty normal,
모두 평번한 것 같은데
but i've got psych evaluations,
high-school records.
근데 심리 평가, 고등학교 기록...
이메일도 보고 있어요
they're reading his e-mails.
tapping his phones.
전화 도청도하고
i've got surveillance photos of perry
here from the hospital yesterday.
어제 페리 병원 감시 사진도 있어요
why are they spending so much
money watching our guy?
왜 페리를 감시하는데 이렇게 많은 돈을 사용 할 까?
i mean, the investigations of
the shooting were done months ago.
총기 사건의 수사는 몇 달 전에 끝났는데 말이죠
see those guys?
저기 사람들 보이지?
개인 청부업자들이야
private contractors.
because it's not about the shooting.
총기 사건 때문에가 아니기 때문이지
the cover-up has nothing
to do with the shooting.
은폐는 총기 사건이랑 전혀 관련이 없어
it's about the trucks.
트럭이랑 관련 있어!
congressman.
-하원의원님
-네
uh, yes?
your support on the next appropriations
bill would be very helpful.
다음 세출 예산안에 도움을 주시면 감사 하겠습니다
we've already earmarked the
no-bid contracts for castleman.
저희는 다음 노빅 계약을 케슬멘에 예약 배정을 했습니다
받을 만 해요
- they deserve it.
- nobody's perfect.
완벽한 사람은 없죠
나자프의 총기 사건한번 문제 보세요
look at all the trouble they had
with that shooting in najaf.
i'm sorry?
무슨 말이시죠?
그런 뉴스는 제가 잘 안 봐서요
i don't really follow
that sort of news.
i just review the contracts.
-전 그냥 계약서를 검토만 하죠
-그러시겠죠
of course.
excuse me.
parker, hardison, bug out,
go back to the office.
파커, 하디슨 나와
병원에 간다
we're going to the hospital.
you need to talk??
-페리랑 다시 말 하시게요?
총기 사건이 실수가 아니였어
the shooting wasn't an accident.
perry isn't a victim. he's a witness.
-페리는 피해자가 아니야, 목격자지
케슬멘이 목격자를 살려두는 회사인거 같아?
castleman strike you
as the kind of company
that wouep a witness alive?
he's not in his damn room.
방에 없잖아
i'm checking all the corridors
외부 출구랑 연결된 모든 복도를 확인 중 이에요
that are connected
to the exterior doors.
sorry, doc,
i know it's closed, but --
죄송해요 의사 선생님. 문 닫은지는 알지만..
mr. ford?
포스씨?
we got to get you out of here now.
-여길 바로 떠나야 합니다
-왜요?
why?
castleman.
케슬멘이요
- ???
- sophie devereaux. ooh!
-페리라 해요
-소피 데보로에요
- ???here we go.
- watch those hands, mr. perry.
손 조심하세요, 페리씨
i'm in a wheelchair.
i'm not blind.
전 휠체어에 있지, 눈먼 게 아니라고요
let's go.
가요
it ain't getting clear.
i can't find --
아무도 없어요
excuse me, do you work on this floor?
실례합니다
이층에서 일하세요?
i, uh -- what floor is this?
여기 몇 층이죠?
전 정형외과에서 일합니다
i'm in orthopedics, so --
hey! hey!
저기요!
get the elevator!
엘리베이터 타!
mr. ford!
포드씨!
hello.
안녕!
aah!
go!
we got all this stuff
one of the castleman hitters.
케스멘의 한 사람으로부터 얻은 거예요
???
더 이상 이렇게 고통스럽게 살 수가 없어요. 죄송해요
this is a suicide note.
-이건 자살 유서인데
-총은 페리 이름 앞으로 등록 되어있어요
this gun is registered
in robert perry's name.
the bill of sale belongs to a
shop a mile from his house.
계산서는 페리 집에서 1킬로 떨어진 가게 것이에요
i got perry squared away in a safe house.
-페리를 안전한 곳으로 옮겨놨어
-장난은 이제 끝이라고요. 이젠 저희를 쫓아 올 거예요
playtime's over, nate.
it's only a matter of time
until they come after us.
the tall one,
the way he used the?nife --
키 큰놈 있죠? 칼 사용하는 걸로 봐서는 전 해병대에요
아마도 전 정찰대 인 것 같아요
ex-marine, probably force recon.
you i.d.'d a guy
off his knife-fightityle?
-칼 쓰는 스타일만 보고 누군지 알겠어?
-특정한 스타일이 있다고
it's a very distinctive style.
다음에 마시려고
that's for later.
i didn't sign up for an this.
전 이런 거 하려고 같이 일한 거 아니에요
what i did before, no got hurt.
예전에 내가 한 일은 아무도 안 다쳤어요
stole paintings for a living.
-전 먹고 살려고 그림 훔쳤어요
-전 사람들 다치게 안 해요
i never hurt anybody.
i actually hurt people, so...
전 사람들 해치니...
nate, if anything
would have happened --
-무슨 일이 일어난다면
-날 부른 건 당신들이 잔아
you know, you guys called me.
you... you remember?
기억나? 팀은 운영해 달라고 간청했고
you begged me to run the crew,
agreed to play by my rules.
내가 하는 대로 한다고 했고
now, walk out if you
have a problem with that.
나가라고 그럼. 문제가 있으면 아무 때나 나가라고!
walk out any day if you
have a problem with that.
it's simple.
we finish this one.
이건 끝내요
just one.
하나 만요
how do we hit 'em?
어떻게 하죠?
congressman jenkins. he's our in.
하원의원 젠킨스. 그를 사용하면 되
he looked me straight in the eye
하지만 내 눈을 보고 총기 사건을 모른다고
and told me he never
even heard of the shooting.
so?
그래서요?
looked me in the eye?
내 눈을 보고?
???they're not looking me in the eye.
남자는 진실을 말 할 때 눈을 보고 말 안하지
men only really look a woman in the eye
남자는 여자한테 거짓말 할 때만 여자 눈을 보지
when they're making
the effort to lie to her.
well, you can't argue with that.
-맞는 말이네요
-올쏘
noted and filed.
all right, jenkins is
dufort's pet congressman.
좋아, 젠킨스가 듀포트의 하윈의원 인거 같은데 미끼를 무는지 볼까
let's see if we can get him to bit
the best way to get two people
to reveal a secret --
2명이 비밀을 폭로 하는데 가장 좋은 방법은
get them to turn on each other.
이간질해서 서로 등을 돌리게 하는거지
may i put that away for you?
제가 갔다 놓을게요?
that didn't sound like a question.
질문 같이 안은데
워싱턴 디시
washington,dc
congressman jenkins.
젠킨스 하원의워님
oh, um.
executive orders, the european company,
익제기티브 오던스, 유럽 회사요
모금 행사 때죠?
from the fund-raiser, right?
that'?right.
모금 행사 때 기억나요. 앉으세요 (로스 엔젤레스)
i remember you from the fund-raiser.
please.(los angeles)
tom abrams. you can call me tommy.
톰 에이브린스인데, 토미라고 불러도 되요
you don't work for
congressman jes, do you?
젠킨스 하원의원님 밑에서 일 하시는 거 아니죠?
i do not.
아니요, 전 북쪽 칼로웨이 하원의원님 밑에서 일합니다
no, i work for congressman
calloway, from ups.
we already have enough friends
on the appropriations committee.
저흰 지출 위원회에 충분한 수의 위원님들이 있습니다
european countries will ahe ud states
in their foreign operations
유럽 회사들은 미국의 외국 활동을 도와주고
수익을 얻을 수 있으면 더 많은 회사들이 도움을 줄 거예요
if they know that european companies
are gonna reap some of the benefits.
some help in the appropriations bill --
-세출 예산안을 도와...
-전 미국 회사를 지지합니다
i support american companies.
- like castleman?
- like castleman.
-케슬멘 같은 회사요?
-케스멜 같은 회사요
and they support, uh, the country.
나라를 도와주죠
well, i'm here because congressman
calloway wanted me to let you know
젠킨스 하원의원님 이제 멀어 졌으니 칼로웨이 하원의원님이
논의할 생각이 있으시다는 걸 전해달라고 해서 왔어요
that he's open to discussions now that
congressman jenkins has gone soft on you.
jenkins al delivers.
-젠킨스 하원의원님은 믿을 만 합니다
-젠킨스 의원님이 제 의원님한테
jenkins told my boss, to his face...
that he's tired of covering for you.
뒷일 처리하는데 짜증난다고 직접 말을 하셨어요
we've backed him for years.
저흰 젠킨스 의원님을 수년 동안 후원했어요
well, jes wanted my
boss to meet this woman
젠킨스 위원은 칼로웨이 의원이 영국회사에서 온 여자 분을 만나달라고 하던데요
from a british company --
eh...uh....
에...에...
executive orders.
익제기트브 오더스
i didn't pick you at random, congressman.
전 위원님을 그냥 뽑은 게 아니에요
castleman can be a fickle friend.
케슬멘이 좀 변덕스러운 회사죠
새로운 친구를 구한다고 하던데요
rumor has it they're
looking for some fresh blood.
i'll tell you what.
만약 당신 회사가 계속 계약에 배정이 되어있고 세출 예산안에 있으면 같이 일하는 거겠지만
if your earmarks
and your no-bid contracts
are still in that appropriations bill,
???
but if they're not,
만약 아니면, 칼로웨이 의원님이 젠킨스 위원님이 누리셨던 모든 호의를 누릴 생각이 있으십니다
well, congressman calloway would
be open to enjoying the same favors
that jenkins has enjoyed
for all these years.
but of course,
jenkins has new friends now.
젠킨스 위원님은 새로운 친구가 생기셨어요
you should look out
for the signs, congressman --
새로운 징후 같은걸 알아차리셔야 되요
missed phone calls...
전화 안 받거나, 자그마한 부탁 안받아주거나
no more little favors.
those are the same signs that
your wife is cheating on you.
-그런 징후는 아내가 바람피우는 징후랑 같은데요
-맞아요
that's right.
and what am i supposed
to do when that happens?
그럼 그런 일이 일어나면 어떻게 하면 되죠, 전?
play the field.
자유롭게 하세요
thanks very much for coming, tommy.
-오셔서 감사합니다, 토미씨
-천만해요
pleasure.
congressman jenkins is very careful.
젠킨스 의원은 아주 조심스러워요
irect bribes,
but he's renovating his house,
직접적인 뇌물은 없는데, 현제까지 60만 달러 이상의 집 리모델링을 5만 달러로 했어
and so far, he's received
over $600,000 worth of work
for a little over 50 grand.
castleman owns the contracting company, huh?
케슬멘이 계약 회사를 아는 거지?
i mean, he's going through like
three shell companies, but, yeah.
3개의 회사를 통해서 하지만, 맞아
this man loves his house.
집 진짜 좋아하는 거 같아
just check out his
web-browsing habits. look here.
인터넷 검색 한건만 봐도 알아
봐봐
you see, the man spthree weeks picking
out the perfect mahogany wood panels.
완벽한 마호가니 나무 벽판을 구하는데 3주나 걸렸어
this site is like wood porn.
-이사이트 꼭 나무 벽판 포르노 사이트 같아
-집 다 완료했어?
is his house finished?
전혀
not even close.
can i owr phone?
전화 빌려죠
hello. yes.
안녕하세요, 마호가니 나무 벽판 주문 좀 취소하려고 하는데요
i'd like to cancel delivery on some
mahogany wood paneling, please.
- ??
- the jenkins house, yeah.
젠킨스의원 집 입니다
you know what, do me a fa man.
그냥 다 취소 해주세요
just go ahead and cancel the whole order.
yes, sir.
what's he doing?
-뭐하는 거야?
-젠킨스 열 받게 하는 거요
yanking the congressman's chain.
aha!
parker started her run yet?
파커 시작했어?
just now.
지금해요
you know, i still think
it would be easier for me
그냥 제가 법안을 해킹하는 게 더 쉬울 꺼 같아요
to just hack the bill
in the printer queue.
no, no. no computers, no.
아니야, 컴퓨터에 없어
법안은 ‘하프’ 라고 불리는 국회의장 나무 박스에 있어
a bill is put into a wooden box on the
congressional floor called the hopper.
a wooden -- whoa, whoa.
a wooden -- a wooden box?
-나무 박스요?
-나무 박스
- a wooden box.
- wood?
oh, we can put a man on the moon,
달에 사람을 보낼 수도 있는데 모든 법안을 나무 박스에 넣어요?
but all our laws
go into a wooden box.
what we need to do is,
we need to get dufort
우리가 지금 필요한건 젠킨스 의원이 케슬멘을 버렸다고 생각하게 하는 거지
to believe that jenkins
is abandoning him,
that jenkins submitted
the appropriations bill
젠킨스가 월래 케슬멘을 위한 법안 없이 세출 예산안을 제출 했다고
that doe have any of the
usual contracts for castleman,
which means that we have to put
our own pages into the bill.
그러려면 법안을 우리가 만든 부분을 넣어야 한다는 뜻인데
that means the only place
that we could get at it wo--
그럴 수 있는 유일한 방법은...
ahh! okay.
- ???
- ??
i mean, break a law,
everybody's done that.
법은 모두 어기죠. 제 어머니도 어겼어요
- my mama's done that.
- uh-huh.
but steal a law...
하지만 법을 훔치는 건. 전설로 남을 꺼야
oh, she's gonna be a legend, baby.
the eagle has landed.
-완료 했어요
-들어갔어
- it's in. uhh!
- go ahead, girl.
오우, 섹시 하다!
sexiness, uhh!
i like it.
you might want to ease up
on that a little bit.
-적절히 하지
-비밀로 해주세요
- i'm just saying,
- yeah.
between me and you.
never leaves the room.
비밀이야
hi, so, how washington?
워싱텅은 어땠어?
well, villains, con men,
wolves in cheep's clothing.
악당, 사기꾼, 양의 탈을 쓴 늑대들. 꼭 집 같았어요
i felt right at home.
this is pretty amazing.
listen to them.
이거 한번 들어 보세요
??this is your
contractor's problem.
무슨 말이에요. 이건 당신 계약사 문제라고요
oh, please. let's not pretend.
-그만 하라고
-법안에 저희 배당을 모두 뺐잖아요
you pulled all our earmarks
from the appropriations...
there's about an hour of this,
but here's the high point.
한 시간 동안 이게 계속돼
여기가 최고에요
somebody screwed up.
i've always been there for you.
누가 망쳐놨어. 난 항상 도와줬다고
i called manila.
마닐라에 전화했고, LA에 세관 통과시켜 줬고
i cleared customs for
you in los angeles.
and that was a risk!
많이 위험 했다고
now, after that,
there's -- it's --
그 후 전화로 부자 버전의 화해를 하죠
well, whatever you call the "rich
guys on telephones" version of makeup sex.
but now we know,
하지만 이젠 알지요
castn makes a thousand shipments a month.
케슬멘이 한 달에 천 번 이상의 화물을 보내는데
but one shipped thromanila,
right after the shooting,
하지만 총기 사건 바로 후 마닐라를 통해서 온 화물
linked to phone records
om the congressman.
의원과 바로 전화 통화
their shipments come through here.
화물이 여기를 통해서 들어 왔어요
now, somewhere in this
madness is container 541.
이 많은 것들 중 화물번호 541이 있어요
it's currently sitting
at the port of los angeles.
-현제 로스앤젤레스 항구에 있어요
-안에 뭐가 있는데?
what's in it?
no idea, but it's moving in two days...
모르겠어요...하지만 2일 후에 항구를 떠날 거예요
heading to the main castleman
storage facility in kansas.
켄사스에 있는 케슬멘 주 창고 시설로 가요
now, that --
저게 페리를 공격한 이유야, 확실해
that's why they tried to hit
perry, right there, that's it.
yeah, wanted to tie up all the loose ends
고국으로 보내기 전에 뒤처리를 마무리를 하고 싶었겠죠
before they tuck this
one away at home base.
what do you ship in a crate from iraq?
이라크에서 화물에 담아서...뭘 보내죠?
oh, boy.
something worth killing for.
사람을 죽일 만한 가치가 있는 거겠지
로스앤젤리스 항구
port of los angeles
how's security?
보안은 어때?
dockyard entrance is no problem.
경비는 문제없어요
there it is. it's 541.
저기 있네, 541번
hold up, rambo.
기다려봐, 람보야
okay, no lasers. no motion detectors.
제이져 없고, 모션 센서, 진동 센서 없고...어
no vibrations, no -- whoops.
왜?
what "whoops"?
there's a webcam.
웹 카메라요.
찍어서 전화로 송출을 하죠
i'm picking up its
broadcast on my phone.
i see it, up on that pole.
저기 있네, 기둥 위에
i just have to spoof the i.p. address
그냥 아이피 바꾸고, 무선 인터넷으로..
and overlay a digital
duplicate on the wi-fi and --
- or that.
- let's go. come on.
아니면 저렇게 하거나..
i'm sorry it was too far
away for you to punch.
손이 안 닫아서 못 부신 게 열 받았겠는데, 미안하다
i'm sure that ally frustrates you.
position one, what's your status?
1번 위치, 현제 상태는
???just done walking the perimeter.
주변 이상 무에요. 오셔도 됩니다
copy that. i'm on my way.
알겠다, 간다
what do you think is in there?
-뭐가 있을 거 같아?
-유물
artifacts from baghdad museums,
바그다드 박물관에서. 아니면 사담 궁에서거나
maybe some from the saddam palaces.
no, i bet it's weapons.
아니야, 무기일거야
a lot of back-alley arms-dealing
going on in a war zone.
전쟁터 뒷골목에서 백만 달러 이상의 무기 거래가 많이 일어나거든
money's good, too.
돈도 괜찮지
hey! line of sight.
이봐, 위치로가. 화물에서 너무 멀리 떨어져 있으면 안되
you shouldn't be away
from that container.
something's wrong with the webcam.
웹 카메라가 이상해요
get some men up therep
and fix that webcam.
누가 올라가서 카메라 고쳐
한 시간 이내로
i want it working in an hour. move.
okay.
그렇치, 이정도면 사람도 죽일만하지
that's worth killing for.
ultraviolet checks out,
paper checks out.
자외선 실험도 통과 했고, 종이도, 워터마크도, 잉크도 모두 괜찮아
the watermarks, the ink,
it all checks out.
there's a whole container of it,
from iraq of all places.
화물 꽉 채워 있고 이라크에서 왔고...
위조가 확실 할 건데
it's got to be counterfeit.
no, it's real.
진짜에요, 진짜같이 느껴져요
it feels(zeal.
hey, what do you got going on?
you and hardison?
워야 진짜, 너하고 하디슨은 누거 괴상한지 경쟁하는거야?
what is it, like a creepy contest?
i don't know, what is it,
$200, $300 million in u.s. currency.
얼마정도지? 2,3백만 미화가 어떻게 이라크에 있는 거지?
what's it doing in iraq?
we sent it there.
-우리가 보냈어
-네?
what?
beginning of the iraq war,
이라크 전쟁 시작 할 때 내가 일하던 전 보험회사가
역사에서 가장 큰 화패 이체를 보험에 드는데 도와줬지
my old company helped insure
the largest currency transfer in history.
billions and billions
in 1s, 5s, and 20s, all cash,
1, 5, 10 달러 현금으로 수입억 달러를 재건하는데 이라크로 보내 줬지
sent to iraq for reconstruction.
bribes.
-뇌물로
-필요한대로
as needed.
$9 billion went missing.
90억 달러가 없어졌어
wait. billion with a "b"?
십, 십억이요?
$9 billion
of u.s. taxpayer money just...
90억의 미국 시민 세금이 그냥 없어 졌어요?
disappeared?
castleman gets a cut of the booty.
케스멘이 일부분을 받는 거죠
the day they go to move it,
이동하는 날, 실제 군인과 이동하는걸 보고
real soldiers,
they see the transfer.
one of the contractors
spooks, starts shooting.
청부업자들은 놀랐고, 총 쏘기 시작하고
yeah, but corporal perry
didn't see anything.
-근데 페리 상등병은 아무것도 못 봤어요
-케슬멘은 모르지 그걸
well, they don't know that.
but castleman's
a billion-dollar company.
케슬멘은 수억 달러의 회사에요
왜 이 돈이 필요하죠?
why would they even care
about this cash?
because it's cash.
왜냐하면, 바로 현금이기 때문이지
you know, money is money.
that's one thing.
돈은 돈이지만, 현금은 완전히 달라
cash is a whole other thing.
for all the money in the economy,
사회에 있는 모든 돈 중 미국인 개인이 가지고 있는 돈은 500 달러뿐이야
there's only about $500 in cash
for every american, that's it.
untraceable small bills --
추적 할 수 없는 소액 지폐, 비밀 자금 대는데 딱 이지
perfect for slush funds, or, um...
improvements for a u.s. congressman.
미 하원의원 집 고쳐 주는 것처럼 말이야
small-time donors,
you know, for re-election.
재선을 위한 소수 액의 기부자들에게 도요
no electrotrail.
흔적이 안남죠
it's money-laundering.
-돈 세탁이야
-어떻게요?
how so?
all right, well,
castleman uses the illegal cash
케슬멘이 불법 현금으로 한원의원의 재선에 사용하고
to re-elect his congressman.
congressman gets him no-bid
contracts for government jobs.
의원이 정부계약을 케슬멘에게 넘기고
and then the government...
정부는 합법적인 돈으로 서비스를 지불하지
...pays for his services
with legal money.
and there's the circle right there.
돌도 도는 거지
they turned the entire u.s. government
into a money-laundering scam.
미국 정부를 이용하는 돈세탁 사기로 바꿨어
- that's right.
- ???i'm impressed.
-맞아
-놀라운데
i never thought i'd say this, ever --
이런 말을 하지는 몰랐지만
that is just way too much money to steal.
훔치지는 너무 많은 돈이야
no, you're not gonna steal it.
훔치지 않을 거야
기억 안나?
you don't remember?
you're the good guys now.
우리 좋은 사람들 이라고 이제
you're gonna give it back.
되돌려 줄거지
로스앤젤레스 항구
port of los angeles
check the perimeter.
주변 확인해봐
start your rounds.
경비 돌아
the car is right othere!
-차 저기 있이
-거기 두 분
- ???you two.
- i told you
셔틀 버스 타고 가자고 했잖아요
we should have taken the shuttle bus.
i paid them $2,000 for food poisoning.
식중독으로 2천 달러 냈다고, 더 이상은 돈 못줘!
they're not getting another cent!
i have to hear this again?
-이말 다시 들어야 돼?
-이봐요, 일로 와봐
hey, hey, you, hey.
come here, come here.
where's the pacifica cruise,
the parking lot?
퍼시픽 주차장이 어디 있죠?
you people have to
move away from this area.
-이곳에서 나가셔야 합니다
-나가려고 하잖아요, 바보야
yeah, well, i'm trying to, jackass.
just tell me where my car is!
-내 자동차가 어디 있는지 말해줘
-또 시작이군
yeah, that's right,
start a fight, why don't you?
- aah!
- ohh!
excuse me.
-실례합니다
-네?
yes, sir?
- hey yes.
- congressman!
의원님
- hello, what a pleasure!
- look, i paid a fortune
이 마호가니 나무 벽판에 돈을 많이 썼다고요
어디 있는지 말해주세요
for these mahogaanels,
and i'd like to know
where the hell they are.
i can help you with
that right here, sir.
네, 도와 드릴게요
they changed the lock.
누가 자물쇠를 바꿨어
just do what you do.
그냥 네가 하는 것 그대로해
i mean, whatever. what you need?
뭐가 필요한데
nah. mnh-mnh.
안 돼
stop all that playin'. mnh-mnh.
하지마
hell no.
after squeezing out three brats --
- aah! here we go again.
- treats me to a little romance,
아 또 시작이군~!
- hey,
- just a little?
거기 두명
경계 위치고 다시 돌아가
hey, you two!
back to your posts.
what's th--
무슨 일이야
- i know you.
- what?
당신 아는데...
???
컨테이너 확인해봐
???where are you go?
어디 갔어?
no.
no, no, no, no, no!
안돼!!
no!
perimeter, perimeter,
출구, 흰 트럭이 거기로 가고 있어
there's a white truck coming at you.
do not let it pass.
통과 하게 놔주지마!
stop that truck.
저 트럭 멈추게 해!
come on, come on.
get out of the way.now!??
차에서 나와! 지금!
get out of the way.
비켜!
grady! what's going in here?
-무슨 일이야?
-여기 왜 왔어요?
what are you doing here?
we're moving the container today.
now, what's happened?
오늘 화물 옮기잖아. 무슨 일이야?
the container's empty.
화물이 비어 있어요
go, go.
get out of the truck.
차에서 나와!
and just where
do you think you're going?
어디갈지 알았어?
i'm just transrting.
그냥 운송하는 중 이에요
no, you're just gonna open this truck.
헌번 트럭 열어보시지
what did you do?
뭐했어?
who the hell are you working for?
도대체 누구 밑에서 일하는 거야?
이 병신 같은 놈아
you stupid son of a bitch!
i will bury you!
죽여 버리겠어
you get your damn hands off me!
손치어
you don't think we kept
all of your e-mails,
네 메일과 전화 기록 없을 꺼 같아?
all of your phone calls?
you go down with us on this.
너도 우리랑 같이 망한다
what is "this"?
-이게 뭐야?
-이게 바로 그 화물이야
this is the container!
the container?
화물?
the container with the iraqi money?
이라크 돈이 있는 화물?
open it.
열어!
okay, i see what this is.
이제 알겠네. 인종 차별이군
this is racial.
this is about my ethniticity, ain't it?
이건 내 인종 때문인 거지? 그렇지?
uh-huh. it's 'cause i'm jewish?
내가 유태인이라서? 응?
i'm supposed to believe that
you just happened to be here
몇 억 달러 현금이 없어진 날 우연히 여기에 왔다는걸 믿으라고?
on the day that a couple of hundred
million dollars in cash goes missing?
hey, don't blame me!
내 탓으로 돌리지마
i helped you smuggle that
money through customs.
세관에 이 돈이 통과하게 도운 건 나라고
i broke laws. i could go to jail!
내가 법을 어겼고, 감옥에 갈 수 있는 사람은 바로 나라고
congressman?
위원님
is this the container, congressman?
이 화물인가요?
- uh,
- what?
you called us, congressman.
-전화 하셨잖아요
-아닌데요
no, no, no, no.
uh, you, uh, must be
mistaken about this.
잘못 아신 것 같은데요
just 'cause a brother
likes matza-ball soup,
흑인이 유태인 스프 좋아 한다고 해서 뭐가 문제 인가요?
what's wrong with that?
sammy davis --
open that door...
문 열어. 아니면 네 머리를 열어 버리지
or i open your head.
not this one. this is 542.
이거 말고요. 이건 542번 이잖아요
what?
your phone call said 541.
전화 하셨을 때는 541번이라 하셨잖아요
sir, you're holding the key.
키 가지고 계시네요
oh, yeah, um...
i'm just back from washington for a day,
워싱턴에서 하루만 갔다 왔는데 직접 와야 하다니
and they say i have to
personally come down here.
give you a map to your
container right there.
여기 화물이 있는 위치 지도고요
and one second. hold on.
i'll get you the key.
키도 여기
- don't. don't.
- they're watching us.
열지 마요. 촬영 중이에요
- they're filming us.
- don't.??
charles, help me here please.
찰스, 좀 도와주게나
no!
congressman, what is all this?
what have you uncovered here?
이게 다 뭔가요, 위원님?
찾아 내신게 뭔가요?
i have uncovered...
부패를 폭로 하겠습니다
corruption.
this is charles dufort
from castleman security.
이 사람은 케슬멘 경비의 찰스 듀포트입니다
and in the course of his company's
very patriotic work in iraq,
이라크에서 애국적으로 활동을 하는 동안에
그는 거대한 미화 절도를 발견하였지요
they discovered a massive
theft of u.s. currency.
our intel revealed
저희 정보에 의하면 이 화물은 저번 달에 이라크를 떠났다고 합니다
that this container left
iraq some time last month.
i knew that i would need high-level
help unraveling this conspiracy,
전 이 음모를 밝히는데 큰 도움이 필요 할 거 같아서
제가 아는 가장 정직한 사람인 젠킨스 의원에게 연락했습니다
so i called the most honest man that i know,
congressman jenkins.
and i want to tell you this --
그리고 전 이걸 확실히 해두고 싶습니다
i, for one, am not going to stand by
전 전쟁으로 수익을 얻는 걸 계속되게 하지 않겠습니다
and let this sort of
war-profiteering continue.
don't you blame me!
내 탓으로 돌리지만
i helped you smuggle
that money through customs.
세관에 이 돈이 통과하게 도운 건 나라고
i broke laws.
i could go to jail!
내가 법을 어겼고, 감옥에 갈 수 있는 사람은 바로 나라고
get your damn hands off me!
손치어
...we kept all of your e-mails,
all of your phone calls?
네 메일과 전화 기록 없을 꺼 같아?
you go down with us.
너도 우리랑 같이 망한다
congressman, is this a confession?
위원님, 이게 자백인가요?
- there's an explanation for everything.
- ???yes, sir,
-설명할 수 있어요
-네 어떻게 설명 하신건가요?
and what is that explanation?
uh...
how long have you been
involved in this smuggling?
이 밀수에 얼마 동안이나 연류 되었죠?
oh, crap.
젠장
we're gonna lead with "crap."
젠장 이래
- what's this about?
- i don't know.
-무슨 일이에요? -포드씨가 여기서 바로 만나자고 하셨어요
mr. ford said he wanted us
down here right away.
hi, guys.
-안녕하세요
-원하시는 게 뭐에요?
what do you want?
show them.
보여줘
an empty truck?
-빈 트럭이요?
-트릭 같은건 없어요
nothing up my sleeve.
- is this stolen?
- not anymore.
-훔친거에요?
-더 이상은 아닙니다
what are we supposed to do with it?
이거 가지고 뭐 하라고요?
pay for corporal perry's rehab.
-페니 상등병의 재활 비용하고
-다른 사람들 비용 지불하세요
and some otxer guys' rehabs.
pretty much whatever you want.
마음대로 하고 싶은 대로요
doc, a cute blonde shows up
with a couple million dollars,
선생님, 귀여운 금발이 몇 백만 달러 가지고와 도와준다는데, 받아요
i say we take the win.
thank you.
감사해요
corporal.
상등병, 감사해요
thank you.
the world doesn't work this way.
세상은 이렇게 돌아가지 않아요
so change the world.
그럼 세상을 바꿔요
* i should know
who i am by now *
okay.
알겠어요
*...the record stands somehow *
* thinking of winter *
we got it, we... we got it.
모두 치료 할 수 있어요 이제
we can take care of everybody.
*while i wait *
i get half, right?
-반은 제거죠
-반이 아니지
no, you don't get half.
yes, i do! i get it half.
anybody who wants to walk
away can do it right now.
이제 그만 하고 싶은 사람은 지금 떠나
* and i remember... *
one more.
한번더..
maybe two.
두 번이나
* of your november downtown *
i bought a plant.
-전 꽃 구입했어요
-좋은데, 팀을 위해서
nice. team spirit.
what does it do?
근데 꽃으로 뭐해?
i can't believe you gave
all your money away.
돈은 다 기부 했다니, 믿을 수가 없어요
you didn't buy yourself anything?
아무 것도 안 샀어요?
i bought a car.
-자동차 샀지
-웨건 샀을 꺼야
probably a station wagon.
- an electric car.
- of course.
-전기차
-귀엽네요. 태엽 감아야 가나요?
how sweet. do you
have to wind it up?
eh, just trying to be responsible.
난 그냥 책임 있게 행동 하려는 거뿐이야
responsible?
책임이요? 좋은 사람이 되는 거 구린 거 아시죠?
you know, it sucks to be the good guy.
you haven't figured it out yet, have you?
아직도 모르네
just 'cause
you're the good guys now...
이제 좋은 사람이라고 해서 가끔씩 즐길 수 없는 건 아니냐
doesn't mean you can't have
a little fun along the way.
whoo-hoo.
- oh, boy. midlife crisis.
- absolutely.
-중년 위기네
-확실해
definitely midlife.
-완전 중년 위기야
-완전해
totally midlife crisis.
중년 위기야
배포는 자유롭게 하시고 출처만 밝혀주세요
마지막 노래는 Joshua Radin의 Winter란 노래네요.
welcome to www.1000fr.com